Guide to the Doris Duke Foundation records, 1934-2009 (bulk 1948-1982)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Subject Files, 1934-2009
  - Voorsanger – Newlin & Maazel: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. See also, Maazel, Lorin and Newlin, Dika, 1937–1952, 1958, 1965 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Waite, Mrs. William W.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1944–1951 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Wayburn, Marguerite: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1955 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Welfare Council of New York City – Central Harlem Street Clubs: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1950 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Westminster Choir College – Beverly Barbee: Donations, Closed Files. Includes photograph, 1958–1959 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Westpfahl, Mrs. Marcia T.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1945–1947, 1954 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Whitehead, Hildreth (Mrs. R.K. Mokrejs): Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1951 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Woman’s Hospital: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1948–1956, 1962 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Wray, Mrs. Margaret – Blair’s Brick House: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1941–1951 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Yorkville Youth Council: Donations, Closed Files, 1956–1958 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Youth Consultation Service: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1966 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Youth Development, Inc.: Donations, Closed Files. Includes 1960 IRS tax exemption, 1962–1963 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Caroline Zachry Institute of Human Development: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1950 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and photographs, 1936–1967 (1 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1936–1967 (2 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1936–1967 (3 of 6) (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1936–1967 (4 of 6) (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1936–1967 (5 of 6) (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Grants-In-Aid, Scholarships – Individuals: Donations, Closed Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1936–1967 (6 of 6) (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - A – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains American Farm School, All Saints School, Adult Retardates Center, American Foundation for the University of the West Indies, American Friends of the Orthodox Patriarchate of Jerusalem, American Humanics Foundation, American-Hungarian Studies Foundation, American Indian History, and American Red Cross in Greater New York, 1951–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - A – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains American Seamen’s Friend Society, American Shakespeare Festival Theater and Academy, American Theater Wing, Anatolia College, Art for World Friendship, Arthritis and Rheumatism Foundation, Association for the Help of Retarded Children, Association Residence for Women, Austrian Chapter of the Knights of Malta, and Adelphi University, 1951–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - American Ballet Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and 1947 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1955–1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - American Council for Émigrés in the Professions (later American Council for Émigré Scholars, Writers, and Artists): Donations, Current Files. Includes 1942,1946, 1949, 1955, and 1970 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - American Council for Émigrés in the Professions (later American Council for Émigré Scholars, Writers, and Artists):Donations, Current Files. Includes 1942, 1946, 1949, 1955, and 1970 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - American Indian Project – Dr. Crampton and Dr. Cash: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1972 tax exemption, 1972–1974 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - American Indian Project – Florida: Donations, Current Files, 1971–1975 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - American Museum of Natural History: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1967 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1952–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - American Museum of Natural History: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1967 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1952–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1929, 1938, 1957, 1965, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1953–1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - The Animal Medical Center: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1967, 1968, and 1969 form 990A tax returns and 1944, 1960, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1959–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - The Animal Medical Center: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1967, 1968, and 1969 form 990A tax returns and 1944, 1960, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1959–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - B – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Dr. Viola W. Bernard, Blinded Veterans Association, Boys’ Club of Durham, Brooklyn Children’s Museum, Brotherhood of New Hope, and Beaudette Foundation, 1952–1969 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Babies Hospital – Presbyterian Hospital: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1944 and 1970 tax exemptions. Doris Duke was a member of the Board of Women Managers beginning in 1935. 1935, 1952–1974 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Berkshire Theatre Festival: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1966 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1966–1974 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Big Sisters: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1936, 1953, 1958, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1951–1973 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Boy Scouts: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1944 and 1954 tax exemptions, 1951–1972 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Boys Harbor: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and 1954 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1955–1975 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Brearley School: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1946, 1970, and 1971 tax exemptions, 1944–1945, 1955–1975 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Brooke, Peter R.: Donations, Current Files. Includes photograph, 1966–1968 (1 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Brooke, Peter R.: Donations, Current Files. Includes photograph, 1966–1968 (2 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - C – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and tax exemptions. Contains Cancer Care (National Cancer Foundation), Campfire Girls, Champaign County Opportunities Industrialization Center, Children’s Day & Night Shelter, Children to Children, Childville, Chinese Women’s Association, City Center of Music and Drama, Clarke School for the Deaf, Congregational Christian Service Center, Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, Corporation for Medical Engineering, and Community Center of Greater New York, 1954–1975 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Chakpori-Ling Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1973 tax exemption, 1973–1974 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Children’s Blood Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1953 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1966–1973 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Chinigo, Michael (DDF Consultant): Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping sand “Report on Authenticity of sources and use of source material by Emanuel M. Josephson, Part II,” 1957–1971 (1 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Chinigo, Michael (DDF Consultant): Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping sand “Report on Authenticity of sources and use of source material by Emanuel M. Josephson, Part II,” 1957–1971 (2 of 2) (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Cinnamon Productions – American Documentary Films, Staten Island Community College: Donations, Current Files. Includes film poster, clippings, and 1957, 1971, and 1972 tax exemptions, 1972–1973 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Clarke, James McClure – Educational and Development Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1956–1968 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Community Council of Greater New York (Formerly Welfare Council of New York City): Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947–1961 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Community Service Society of New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1952–1972 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Contemporary Music Society: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and 1955 tax exemption, 1957–1959 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1952 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1954–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Council on Social Work Education: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1952 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1954–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - D – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Denver Urban League, Disabled American Veterans, Ruth S. Davis (Documentary Film Project), Asa J. Davis, Durham Community Chest, Durham Y.W.C.A., Durham-Orange County Medical Foundation, Mrs. James H. Dukes, and Alvin Ailey American Dance Theater (Dance Theater Foundation), 1951–1968 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Davison, Dr. W.C. (Duke University Medical Center Dean; Vice President of DDF): Donations, Current Files, 1954–1961 (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Davison, Dr. W.C. (Duke University Medical Center Dean; Vice President of DDF): Donations, Current Files, 1954–1961 (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Davison, Dr. W.C. (Duke University Medical Center Dean; Vice President of DDF): Donations, Current Files, 1960–1973 (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Davison, Dr. W.C. (Duke University Medical Center Dean; Vice President of DDF): Donations, Current Files, 1960–1973 (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Davison, Dr. W.C. – Professorship in Pediatrics and Death: Donations, Current Files, 1971–1972 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Deafness Research Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1959 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1951–1973 (1 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Deafness Research Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1959 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1951–1973 (2 of 2) (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Doylestown Foundation (Formerly Jonzel Foundation) – Dr. Rose: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1959 tax exemption, 1959–1960, 1966, 1972 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Duke Hospital – Social Service Department: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1952–1966 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Duke Office – 505 Park Avenue: Donations, Current Files. Contains administrative and financial information regarding DDF, 1951–1975 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Duke University School of Medicine – Pre-Natal Training Program: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1953–1973 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - E – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Contains Eastern Paralyzed Veterans Association, Allen H. Eaton, Fort Greene Community Progress Center (Economic Opportunity Committees), Indiana University (Educational Motion Pictures), and Educational Testing Service, 1952–1967 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - East Harlem Protestant Parish Narcotics Program – Exodus House: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1956, 1965, 1968, 1969, and 1971 tax exemptions, 1958–1975 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Elder Craftsmen: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and1957 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1957–1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Eye Bank for Sight Restoration: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1956 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1952–1974 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - F – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Wesley Fach, First Baptist Church of Nutley, N.J., Foundation Library Center, Foster Parents’ Plan for War Children, Katherine Dunham School of Dance (Foundation for the Preservation and Development of the Cultural Arts), Free Milk Fund for Babies, Herald Tribune Fresh Air Fund, Friars Annual Benefit Dinner, Frost & Sullivan ,and Fund for Asia, 1950–1974 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Federations of Protestant Welfare Agencies: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1962 and 1970 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1951–1975 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Foundation for Mind Research: Donations, Current Files. Includes and 1967 tax exemption, 1971–1974 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Foundations: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings. Contains information on legislation affecting charitable organizations, 1958–1973 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Fountain House: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, photographs, and 1949, 1950, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1964–1972 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - French Management Company – Swizberger-Rolfe: Donations, Current Files. Includes Leases for offices at 595 Madison Avenue, New York, New York and related correspondence, 1953–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - French Management Company – Swizberger-Rolfe: Donations, Current Files. Includes Leases for offices at 595 Madison Avenue, New York, New York and related correspondence, 1953–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - G – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and tax exemptions. Contains Gracie Square Boys’ Club-Girls’ Club, Girls Club of New York, Max Glass (Department of Welfare, City of New York), Martha Graham Foundation for Contemporary Dance, and Greer-A Children’s Community, 1953–1968 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1944 and 1970 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, 1944 and 1970 tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Goodwill Industries of New York and New Jersey: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and 1944 and 1955 tax exemptions, 1955–1969 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - H – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and tax exemptions. Contains Hebrew Day Nursery, Highlander Folk Art, Home Advisory Council of New York, Miriam Hall (Cartlane Poodle Kennels),Hampton Day School, Holyland Center, Honolulu Symphony Society, Karen Horney Clinic, and Hunter College, 1951–1975 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Honolulu – Honolulu Academy of Arts, Honolulu Community Chest, and United Welfare Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1941–1964 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Hospitalized Veterans Service of the Musicians Emergency Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1954 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1959–1972 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Human Resources Center: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1957 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1959–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Human Resources Center: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1957 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1959–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Humane Society of the United States: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1960 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1960–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Humane Society of the United States: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1960 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1960–1975 (2 of 2) (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - I – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Contains Viola Ilma, International Wildlife Conservation Society, and Inwood House, 1950–1969 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Institute for the Crippled and Disabled: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1964 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Institute of Biomagnetics: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1962 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1951, 1964–1971 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Institute of Living: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1946 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1968–1973 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - International Center of Photography: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and 1974 tax exemption, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - International Institute for the Perception of Gospel Music and the Arts: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1975 tax exemption, 1975 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - International Rescue Committee – Angier Biddle Duke: Donations, Current Files Includes clippings, photographs, and 1955 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1955–1975 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - International Rescue Committee – Children’s Home, Hainbach, Austria: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and 1955 and 1970 tax exemptions, 1957–1970 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - International Social Service: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs, 1970tax exemption, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1971 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - J – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Contains William S. Jackson, Johns Hopkins Fund & University, Judson Health Center, and Just One Break, 1952–1973 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - K – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Kessler Institute for Rehabilitation, Kauikeolani Children’s Hospital, Ray Kinney, Knickerbocker Ball Foundation, Joseph S. Kornfeld Memorial Library Alcove, and Krebiozen Research Foundation, 1947–1975 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - L – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Robert E. Lee Memorial Association, Lexington School for the Deaf, La Mama Experimental Theater Club, and Lennox Hill Hospital, 1967–1973 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Legal Aid Society: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1943, 1965, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1952–1976 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association: Donations, Current Files, 1952–1969, 1973–1974 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Mc – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1965 tax exemption. Contains Cardinal McCloskey School and Home, 1968 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - McBean, Mrs. Leta (Board Member): Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1947, 1953–1974 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - M – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Manhattan School of Music, Manhattanville Community Centers, Maryknoll Fathers, Julie Medlock (Public Interest), Mental Health Film Board, Metropolitan Museum of Art, Morris Theater Foundation, Camp Morris, Katherine Morton, and Mt. Zion African Methodist Episcopal Church, 1952–1969 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Maimonides Medical Center – Dr. Krippner’s Project: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and 1970 and 1971 tax exemptions, 1971–1973 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Maryknoll Sisters: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1940 and 1961 tax exemptions, 1956–1971 (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Maryknoll Sisters: Donations, Current Files. Includes clippings, photographs, and 1940 and 1961 tax exemptions, 1956–1971 (2 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - N – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, photographs, and tax exemptions. Contains National Association for Retarded Children, National Society of Interior Designers, National Catholic Society for Animal Welfare, National Catholic Welfare Conference (Catholic Relief Services), National Citizens Committee for the World Health Organization, National Council of the Churches of Christ in the United States of America, National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis (Greater New York Women’s Division), National Pollution Control Foundation, National Recreation and Park Association, and National Society for the Prevention of Blindness, 1947–1975 (1 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - N – Miscellaneous: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains National Variety Artists/Negro Actors Guild of America, Neighborhood Day Nursery of Harlem, New York Diet Kitchen Association (Children’s Health Service), New York Foundling Hospital, New York Friends Center, New York Heart Association, New York University, North-Eastern Dispensary, and Nyingma Institute, 1947-1975 (2 of 2) (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - N.A.A.C.P. – Legal Defense and Education Fund: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, 1940 and 1970 tax exemptions, correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., and correspondence with Thurgood Marshall, 1950–1971 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - National Association for Practical Nurse Education: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1946, 1962, and 1970 tax exemptions, 1957–1974 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - National Committee on Alcoholism: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1945 and 1951 tax exemptions, 1955–1972 (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - National Committee on Alcoholism: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1945 and 1951 tax exemptions, 1955–1972 (2 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - National Information Bureau: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1970 and 1971 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1943–1974 (1 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - National Information Bureau: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1970 and 1971 tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1943–1974 (2 of 2) (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - National League for Nursing: Donations, Current Files, 1955–1956 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - National Travelers Aid Association: Donations, Current Files. Includes correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1949–1953, 1975 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - National Youth Science Foundation: Donations, Current Files. Includes photograph and 1960 tax exemption, 1961–1963 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - Nature Conservancy: Donations, Current Files. Includes 1966 tax exemption, 1968–1970 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - Near East College Association: Donations, Current Files. Includes photographs and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc., 1950–1961, 1966 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains Relief Hose Company No. 2 (Raritan, N.J.), Benevolent and Protective Order of Elks – Watchung Hills Lodge No. 2252, Hillsborough Boys Football Association, Hillsborough Little League, Hillsborough Reformed Church, Bonnie Brae Farm for Boys, The Seeing Eye, Red Cross Drive of Hillsborough Township, Hillsborough Township Volunteer Fire Company, First Aid and Rescue Squad of Somerville, Hillsborough First Aid and Rescue Squad, and Doris Duke Personal Fund gifts, 1937–1974 (1 of 4) (Box 74, Folder 2)
  - New Jersey: Donations, Current Files. Includes tax exemptions. Contains Raritan First Aid Squad, Hillsborough Township Volunteer Fire Company, Hillsborough First Aid and Rescue Squad, and Somerset Valley Visiting Nurse Association, 1937–1974 (2 of 4) (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - New Jersey: Donations, Current Files. Includes clipping, photograph, tax exemptions, and correspondence with Independent Aid, Inc. Contains South Branch Watershed Association, American Cancer Society (Somerset County chapter), American Red Cross (Raritan Valley chapter), and First Aid and Rescue Squad of Somerville, 1937–1974 (3 of 4) (Box 74, Folder 4)